{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Programming language used in web development",
            "answer": "javascript"
        },
        {
            "question": "Game involving guessing words",
            "answer": "hangman"
        },
        {
            "question": "Creating and maintaining software",
            "answer": "programming"
        },
        {
            "question": "A markup language for creating web pages",
            "answer": "html"
        },
        {
            "question": "A stylesheet language used for describing the presentation of a document",
            "answer": "css"
        },
        {
            "question": "JavaScript library for building user interfaces",
            "answer": "react"
        },
        {
            "question": "A version control system",
            "answer": "git"
        },
        {
            "question": "A platform for version control and collaboration",
            "answer": "github"
        },
        {
            "question": "A tool for automating web development tasks",
            "answer": "gulp"
        },
        {
            "question": "A popular package manager for JavaScript",
            "answer": "npm"
        },
        {
            "question": "A widely used front-end framework for web development",
            "answer": "bootstrap"
        },
        {
            "question": "A JavaScript runtime built on Chrome's V8 engine",
            "answer": "nodejs"
        },
        {
            "question": "A popular relational database management system",
            "answer": "mysql"
        },
        {
            "question": "A NoSQL database program",
            "answer": "mongodb"
        },
        {
            "question": "A language used for structuring and presenting content on the web",
            "answer": "xml"
        },
        {
            "question": "A language for querying databases",
            "answer": "sql"
        },
        {
            "question": "A command-line interface for interacting with a computer's operating system",
            "answer": "bash"
        },
        {
            "question": "A platform for building mobile and desktop applications using web technologies",
            "answer": "electron"
        },
        {
            "question": "A CSS preprocessor",
            "answer": "sass"
        },
        {
            "question": "A JavaScript framework for building server-side applications",
            "answer": "express"
        }
    ]
}
